Guide to the Witold Gombrowicz Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile, 24.22; (20 boxes)
  - OVERSIZE
    - Box 85, folder 1857 (Box 130, Folder 2413)
    - Box 85, folder 1858 (Box 130, Folder 2414)
    - Box 85, folder 1862 (Box 130, Folder 2415)
    - Box 86, folder 1870 (Box 130, Folder 2416)
    - Box 86, folder 1871 (Box 130, Folder 2417)
    - Box 86, folder 1872 (Box 130, Folder 2418)
    - Box 86, folder 1877 (Box 130, Folder 2419)
    - Box 87, folder 1880 (Box 130, Folder 2420)
    - Box 87, folder 1888 (Box 130, Folder 2421)
    - Box 88, folder 1892 (Box 131, Folder 2422)
    - Box 88, folder 1895 (Box 131, Folder 2423)
    - Box 88, folder 1896 (Box 131, Folder 2424)
    - Box 88, folder 1897 (Box 131, Folder 2425)
    - Box 88, folder 1898 (Box 131, Folder 2426)
    - Box 89, folder 1900 (Box 131, Folder 2427)
    - Box 89, folder 1901 (Box 131, Folder 2428)
    - Box 89, folder 1904 (Box 131, Folder 2429)
    - Box 89, folder 1906 (Box 131, Folder 2430)
    - Box 90, folder 1907 (Box 131, Folder 2431)
    - Box 90, folder 1909 (Box 131, Folder 2432)
    - Box 90, folder 1910 (Box 132, Folder 2433)
    - Box 91, folder 1911 (Box 132, Folder 2434)
    - Box 92, folder 1926 (Box 132, Folder 2435)
    - Box 96, folders 1949-1950 (Box 132, Folder 2436-2438)
    - Box 99, folder 1960 (Box 133, Folder 2439-2440)
    - Box 100, folder 1969 (Box 133, Folder 2441)
    - Box 101, folder 1971 (Box 133, Folder 2442)
    - Box 101, folder 1972 (Box 133, Folder 2443)
    - Box 101, folder 1974 (Box 133, Folder 2444)
    - Box 102, folder 1978 (Box 133, Folder 2445)
    - Box 102, folder 1981 (Box 133, Folder 2446)
    - Box 103, folder 1984 (Box 133, Folder 2447)
    - Box 104, folder 1997 (Box 133, Folder 2448)
    - Box 105, folder 1998 (Box 134, Folder 2449)
    - Box 106, folder 2011 (Box 134, Folder 2450)
    - Box 106, folder 2015 (Box 134, Folder 2451)
    - Box 106, folder 2019 (Box 134, Folder 2452)
    - Box 106, folder 2020 (Box 134, Folder 2453)
    - Box 106, folder 2021 (Box 134, Folder 2454)
    - Box 106, folder 2022 (Box 134, Folder 2454a)
    - Box 107, folder 2024 (Box 134, Folder 2455)
    - Box 107, folder 2027 (Box 134, Folder 2456)
    - Box 107, folder 2028 (Box 134, Folder 2457)
    - Box 108, folder 2034 (Box 134, Folder 2458)
    - Box 108, folder 2036 (Box 134, Folder 2459)
    - Box 108, folder 2044 (Box 134, Folder 2460)
    - Box 109, folder 2045 (Box 135, Folder 2461)
    - Box 109, folder 2046 (Box 135, Folder 2462)
    - Box 109, folder 2048 (Box 135, Folder 2463)
    - Box 109, folder 2049 (Box 135, Folder 2464)
    - Box 109, folder 2050 (Box 135, Folder 2465)
    - Box 109, folder 2052 (Box 135, Folder 2466)
    - Box 109, folder 2054 (Box 135, Folder 2467)
    - Box 109, folder 2062 (Box 135, Folder 2468)
    - Box 109, folder 2063 (Box 135, Folder 2469)
    - Box 110, folder 2159 (Box 136, Folder 2470)
    - Box 110, folder 2161 (Box 136, Folder 2471)
    - Box 110, folder 2162 (Box 136, Folder 2472)
    - Box 110, folder 2163 (Box 136, Folder 2473)
    - Box 112, folder 2185 (Box 136, Folder 2474)
    - Box 112, folder 2186 (Box 136, Folder 2475)
    - Box 112, folder 2187 (Box 136, Folder 2476)